Abhijeet Chatterjee

Kanpur Nagar, Uttar Pradesh, India



abhijeet007rocks8@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/abhijeet-chatterjee-445aa2195

Summary

Currently I am an Engineering Student pursuing B.Tech in Computer Science.

5 star JAVA

5 star Python

5 star C++

4 star problem solving

on Hackerrank.

https://www.hackerrank.com/abhijeet007rock1

3 on CodeChef

I have some hands on experience in website development and android development and in search for projects to showcase my skills.

Experience



MedTourEasy Oct 2020 - Nov 2020 (2 months)



Content Writer

MyPustak.com Aug 2020 - Oct 2020 (3 months)

Education



VIT_Vellore Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, CSE-Core 2019 - 2023



Mercy Memorial School

Intermediate, Science stream with Computer Science 2017 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications



IBM Blockchain Essentials V2 - IBM

- Data Science Foundations Level 1 IBM
- Python for Data Science IBM
- Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Py University of Michigan 8E9VPM5EGA4K
- HTML, CSS, and Javascript for Web Developers The Johns Hopkins University YSKG8CNZTPAK
- A Crash Course in Data Science The Johns Hopkins University RCXVVUYPHD44
- Technical Support Fundamentals Coursera
 ALSQCH932R5L
- Programming Fundamentals Coursera Course Certificates
 RCXJKASMVYYU
- Teamwork Foundations LinkedIn
- Embracing Unexpected Change LinkedIn
- m What is Graphic Design? LinkedIn
- Project Management Foundations: Teams LinkedIn
- Writing a Resume LinkedIn

Skills

Python (Programming Language) • HTML • Java • Software Development • Web Development • Data Structures • Data Analysis • Web Design • Programming • Computer Science